Voice of Shadows is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Nicholas Bain.
A young working class woman stands to inherit an estate if she and
her boyfriend abide by a set of bizarre stipulations.
Gabriel, played by Guillermo Blanco.
Emma, played by Corrinne Mica.
Celeste, played by María José Vargas Agudelo.
Milda, played by Jane Hammill.
Father John, played by Michael Paul Levin.
Ernesto, played by Martin Harris.
Dark Shadows is a 2012 Gothic dark fantasy comedy horror film based
on the Gothic television soap opera of the same name.
Directed by Tim Burton, the film stars Johnny Depp alongside Michelle Pfeiffer, Eva Green, Jackie Earle Haley,
Jonny Lee Miller, Chloë Grace Moretz, Helena Bonham Carter, and Bella Heathcote in a dual role.
Christopher Lee has a small role in the film, marking his 200th film
appearance and his fifth and final collaboration with Burton.
Jonathan Frid, star of the original Dark Shadows series, makes a cameo
appearance, and died shortly before the film was released.
One of the film's producers, Richard D.
Zanuck, died two months after its release.
The film had a limited release on May 10, 2012, and was
officially released the following day in North America.
It performed poorly at the United States box
office, but did well in foreign markets.
Reviews for the film were mixed; critics praised its visual style and consistent humor,
but felt it lacked a focused or substantial plot and developed characters.
The film explores themes of gothic horror, vengeful ghost, catholic priest.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.